<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Red Team 
 DevOps Project</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Red Team 
 DevOps Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 14:18:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dev Team</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/devteam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 14:18:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/devteam/</guid>
      <description>Janelle Cavazos
Jacob Judd
Jeffrey Blackard
Nathan Taylor
Sean McKenney
Stephanie Chheng
We developed this using an AWS box that is running Hugo v0.53. This is used as our development box. It was easy to set up and free to use. Working together to build a website on AWS was a great learning experience and is interesting to see how development works without direct communication between both teams.
¯\_(ツ)_/¯</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ops Team</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/opsteam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 14:18:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/opsteam/</guid>
      <description>Abdul Khan
Anthony Basile
Brie Bracknett
Bryce Burwitz
Eddie Alvarado
Elys Truong
William Nguyen
We decided on using Pythonanywhere as our production environment, as it was a easy to use, and free service for the size project that we are committing to. Python anywhere has a simplistic basis for uploading files, and allowing WebApps to function on its system. Working as the Ops team was interesting, as it was a disconnect between the development of the code, and the final production phase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1 - Red Team</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 14:18:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>GROUP PROJECT #1: Deploy a webapp, oldstyle
The class will be divided into groups of 6–10 students each. These groups will be split into Dev and Ops teams. Each group is responsible to deliver a running Python webapp (e.g., Hyde, Hugo, etc.) by the due date. The application must be modified in some way so that the appearance of the interface is visibly different from the default code as published on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>